Hello friends, everyone knows that Deepak
Nitrite and Aarti Industries are
excellent companies in the chemical sector. These are excellent
stocks. But friends,
if we have to select one of these two, then which
stock will we select? For this, let us
compare this stock of theirs. Okay, let us
see in the video. Friends, let us
see their returns, how much has it been and
compare it with the returns of BSE Midcap Index and BSE Sensex. So you can see that
Deepak Nitrate has given a return of 94.57 percent in 1 year returns.
Friends,
Deepak Nitrate has given a return of
34.6 percent in this year and BSE Midcap has given a
return of 20.50 percent in its -
and BSE Sensex has also
given a return of - 23.33 percent in -. Now let us look at three years.
Deepak Nitrite is doing business in theatres
because 7.1 percent analysis
friends and the economic outlook has given 34.83 percent in its -
BSE Midcap -
125  Deepak Nitrite has given a five-year return of 50.79% and BSE Sensex has given a five-
year return of 50.79%. Aarti Industries has
performed slightly better here and has given a
45.92% return. BSE
Midcap has given a total positive return of 2.2%
and BSE has given a 3.14% positive
return. Now let's look at the 10-year period. In
2020, the analyzed return of Deepak Nitrite in 10 years has been
41.0% and
Aarti Industries has given a 40.72% return. So,
friends, in the 10-year range, Aarti
Industries has performed better than Deepak Nitrite
and BSE Midcap has given a
5.27% return and BSE Sensex has given a 65% return.
Friends, we are talking about the society. Today is
May 8, 2020. This is the date of today. So, friends,
you can see that both these companies are
giving almost good performance. Now, the data inside these  Let's
reduce it to friends, now if we
talk about their market cap, Deepak
Nitrite's market cap is 7200.51 point
34 crore rupees, while its market
cap is 18500.565.84 crore rupees, so
according to the market cap, the
company is two and a half times bigger than Deepak Nitrite, friends, now let's look at their debt,
they must have taken loans to
run their business, that is also very important, we have to
see how much debt is on this company, so
you can see Deepak Nitrite's debt is
1186.52 crore rupees, whereas Aarti
Industries has 2400.150 crore rupees, so even if we
work, it is almost the same, and let's
see here, if you are drinking, then friends,
Deepak Nitrite wins on the victims' front,
its back is 15.0.57 and from the
economic point of view, Grand Prix Race on 35.0, so
friends, Deepak Nitrite's PSO is
almost two times cheaper from the economic point of view, so
this store is
getting half cheaper than Aarti Industries, friends,
here Deepak  Nitrite, it looks good,
it is at an attractive valuation, right now
Deepak Nitrate, while Aarti Industries, it is
expensive elevation, so friends, this has been
their record here, their
record of returns has been that the market is, now see, after
drinking them, we will tell you, the
video of the fundamentals of Nitrite and Aarti Industries and their financials is also available on our YouTube channel,
which is put in a playlist, the
name of the playlist is Chemical and For Stock,
friends, you can subscribe to our YouTube channel
and
you can see all those videos in the playlist, if you liked our video, then
like and share it as much as possible,
thank you friends.